You can find me in New York City, and today I'm going to teach you how to play a saw.
There are many ways to hold the saw while playing.
The most prevalent way is to sit down, place the handle between your knees, and clasp your knees together so that the blade will not slip through.
If you are right handed then you hold the tip of the blade with your left hand.
This is the most popular stance.
However, some people play standing up.
You hold the saw in the same manner, but you stand up.
Some people, mostly I found Switzerland, play the saw kneeling down.
Again, you hold the handle between your knees, but you're kneeling down.
Some kneel down this way.
Whatever way you decide to hold your saw, it doesn't matter.
The sound production method is the same; it's just a different stance.